<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>

	<name>Yes, Vehicles, Finally!</name>
	<author>Mason J. Caboose, NinjaSiren</author>
	<supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
	</supportedVersions>
    <url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=48126.0</url>
	<description>
	    [v0.83 Patch #3]
        A true implementation of vehicles into RimWorld!
    
        First off, a big thank you to Jecrell and Neronix, without him none of you would have this!
    
        Second thing, thank you to Mason J. Caboose for making the original mod! I really wanted vehicles in the game, I ended up continuing this mod!
    
	    Thirdly, thank you to Hjkma for helping me fix the Combat Extended patch!
	
        This mod is a 'simple' implementation of a truck into our lovely rim world, you can load crew, passengers, turrets, and equipment for both crossing the map and for caravanning.
    
        To acquire a vehicle you need to research Machining and Smithing for the Vehicle Table. Here you can construct a box filled with appropriately named pieces.
        After following guides 1-Z on your ikea manual and throwing away the last 5 screws your pawn will have succesfully assembled a working scrap heap!
    
        Just like any partially oiled machine, youll have to fill and power it with Chemfuel! (not included)
    
        Upon assigning a driver, you must instruct the vehicle to draft itself for glorious duty.
		
        ==Notes and Help==
    
        - If your goal is caravanning, please put a driver at least with good mood and no needs.
        - New game is optional, but maybe needed. (Old saves without this mod or updates may break game saves.)
        - No one else should show up on your door with any of this stuff.
        - You need both a gunner and a driver to fight.
        - Only the machine gun turret fits on the Truck and ATV.
        - Bugs is possibly plenty in this mod, but hopefully that it woudn't to break your game!
		
		==Version changelog==
		
		- Updated the armor values as per change of Combat Extended.
		
    </description>
</ModMetaData>
